<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data noupdate="1">

        <record id="disease_disease_1" model="disease.disease">
            <field name="name">Fusarium Wilt</field>
            <field name="description">
                Fusarium wilt is a fungal disease that affects a wide range of crops, including
                tomatoes, bananas, and cucumbers. It is caused by various species of the Fusarium fungus and is
                characterized by the wilting and yellowing of leaves, stunted growth, and eventual death of the plant.
                The fungus infects the plant's vascular system, obstructing the flow of water and nutrients.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="disease_disease_2" model="disease.disease">
            <field name="name">Late Blight</field>
            <field name="description">
                Late blight is a devastating disease that affects potatoes and tomatoes. It is
                caused by the water mold Phytophthora infestans and can spread rapidly under cool and moist conditions.
                Symptoms include dark, water-soaked lesions on leaves, stems, and fruits, which can quickly turn into
                brown or purplish-black patches. The disease can lead to the complete destruction of the crop if not
                controlled.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="disease_disease_3" model="disease.disease">
            <field name="name">Powdery Mildew</field>
            <field name="description">
                Powdery mildew is a fungal disease that affects a wide range of plants, including
                grapes, cucurbits, and roses. It appears as a white or gray powdery growth on the surfaces of leaves,
                stems, and flowers. Infected plants may experience stunted growth, distorted leaves, and reduced fruit
                production. Warm and humid conditions favor the development and spread of powdery mildew.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="disease_disease_4" model="disease.disease">
            <field name="name">Rust</field>
            <field name="description">
                Rust is a fungal disease that affects many cereal crops, including wheat, barley,
                and corn. It appears as orange, brown, or reddish-brown powdery pustules on the surfaces of leaves,
                stems, and grains. Infected plants may exhibit stunted growth, yellowing of leaves, and reduced yield.
                Rust can spread rapidly, especially in humid conditions, and can cause significant damage to
                crops.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="disease_disease_5" model="disease.disease">
            <field name="name">Bacterial Spot</field>
            <field name="description">
                Bacterial spot is a common disease that affects a wide range of vegetable crops,
                such as tomatoes, peppers, and cucumbers. It is caused by different species of bacteria, including
                Xanthomonas and Pseudomonas. Symptoms include small, water-soaked lesions on leaves, stems, and fruits,
                which can enlarge and turn dark over time. Infected fruits may develop rot and become
                unmarketable.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="disease_disease_6" model="disease.disease">
            <field name="name">Citrus Canker</field>
            <field name="description">
                Citrus canker is a bacterial disease that affects citrus trees, including oranges,
                lemons, and grapefruits. It is caused by the bacterium Xanthomonas citri subsp. citri. The disease is
                characterized by raised corky lesions on leaves, stems, and fruits, often surrounded by an oily or
                water-soaked margin. Severe infections can cause defoliation, premature fruit drop, and reduced tree
                vigor.
            </field>
        </record>


    </data>
</odoo>