<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data noupdate="1">

        <record id="land_preparation_process" model="process.process">
            <field name="name">Land Preparation</field>
            <field name="description">
                * Clear the land of any existing vegetation.
                * Plow the soil to loosen it and break up any compacted layers.
                * Level the field to ensure uniformity and proper water drainage.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="seed_planting_process" model="process.process">
            <field name="name">Seed Planting</field>
            <field name="description">
                * Plant the seeds in the prepared soil using direct seeding (sowing seeds directly into the soil) or
                transplanting seedlings grown in nurseries.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="irrigation_process" model="process.process">
            <field name="name">Irrigation</field>
            <field name="description">
                * Regularly monitor soil moisture levels and adjust irrigation schedules accordingly to ensure optimal
                water supply.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="fertilization_process" model="process.process">
            <field name="name">Fertilization</field>
            <field name="description">
                * Conduct soil tests to determine the nutrient content and pH level of the soil.
                * Select appropriate fertilizers based on the nutrient requirements of the crop and the soil analysis
                results.
                * Apply fertilizers, either organic (such as compost or manure) or synthetic (nitrogen, phosphorus, and
                potassium fertilizers), to provide essential nutrients for crop growth.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="weed_control_process" model="process.process">
            <field name="name">Weed Control</field>
            <field name="description">
                * Regularly inspect the field for weed growth and take timely action to prevent weeds from competing
                with crops for resources.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="pest_disease_management_process" model="process.process">
            <field name="name">Pest and Disease Management</field>
            <field name="description">
                * Monitor crops regularly for signs of pests and diseases.
                * Implement integrated pest management strategies, including cultural practices (crop rotation,
                companion
                planting), biological control (introducing predators or parasites), and chemical pesticides if
                necessary.
                * Employ appropriate disease control measures such as crop rotation, resistant varieties, or targeted
                pesticide application.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="crop_monitoring_management_process" model="process.process">
            <field name="name">Crop Monitoring and Maintenance</field>
            <field name="description">
                * Continuously observe the crops for growth, development, and signs of stress or disease.
                * Prune or thin plants as needed to promote healthy growth and airflow.
                * Stake or provide support structures for plants that require additional support.
                * Apply growth regulators or hormones if necessary to manage crop growth or flowering. </field>
        </record>


    </data>
</odoo>